（発射音）
（銃撃音）
（ティト）
くそったれ！
どうなってやがる
Damn it! What the hell's going on?
（少年兵）
さっさとぶっ殺せ！
Just kill him already!
I'm killing him, but he won't die!
（少年兵）
殺しても死なねぇんだよ！
There's only one of him!
（少年兵）
敵は１人だろうが！
やつは例のバケモンだ！
He's the monster everyone's talking about!
That government scum is
sending in monsters!
（少年兵）
政府のクソどもが
バケモンよこしやがった！
-Stop screwing around!
-Aim for his head!
（少年兵）
ふざけんな！
頭狙え！　頭！
（銃声）
うあああ！
Go! Kill him!
行け！　ぶっ殺せ！
He's mine!
（ティト）
やってやる！
（少年兵たちの叫び声）
（少年兵）
はっ はっ… がっ！
うわっ！
ひっ ひいっ…
はぁ はぁ はぁ…
Hey.
（下士官）
おい
Get back out there.
下がるな
ひっ！
やつは神の兵だ！　神の…
He's a soldier of God! God's--
（銃声）
（少年兵）ああっ… ひっ
（下士官）
下がるな！
I said, get back out there!
ひっ…
くっ…
うっ ううっ…
はぁっ はぁっ はぁっ…
（叫び声）
（銃声）
何が神の兵だ！
Some soldier of God.
ざまあみろ！　ざまあみろ！
ざまあみろ！
Take that! And that.
神をぶっ殺してやったぜ！
I killed God!
はぁっ… え…
あ…
あ… あ…
ああっ…
（銃声）
（ティト）うわあっ！
（戦闘機の音）
（指揮官）
急げ！　急げ！　急げ！　急げ！
Go, go, go!
（刺さる音）
AJIN: DEMI-HUMAN
深く眠れるかい？
傷は癒せたかい？
Do you sleep well?
Did your wounds heal?
Just cos' they say the night is lonely
夜が寂しいからって
無理して
誰かを愛さないで
You don't have to force yourself
To love someone
They say I'm dreaming
夢を見る事だって
咽び泣く事だって
They say I'm sobbing
知りもしないまま
死んでみたって
They say I tried to die without knowing
上手に隠れたかい？
息は潜めたかい？
Did you manage to hide?
Did you hold your breath?
今が苦しいからって
Just cos' they say it's tough now
You don't have to force yourself to change
無理して自分を変えないで
Even a brave savage
勇敢な蛮人だって
悩める子羊だって
Even a troubled lamb
回り道して生きているって
They are just wandering through life
目立たないように
So I don't stand out
So I can put up with it
堪えられるように
So my train of thought won't stop yet
思考回路はまだ
止めないように
Tonight run away, run a way
It's unbelievable
今宵 RUN AWAY RUN A WAY
嘘みたいだ
誰かこの手
掴んでくれよ
Someone take my hand
見えない明日は来なくていい
The tomorrow we can't see
Doesn't have to come
今はただ 眠りたい
Now I just want to sleep
WHAT'S THAT STUFF HAVE TO DO WITH US?
（アラーム音）
（ドアの開閉音）
UNIVERSITY EXAM PREPARATION
Saturday is the standardized
practice exam, right? How's it going?
（圭(けい)の母）
土曜日は統一模試よね？
調子はどう？
（永井圭(ながいけい)）
うん　大丈夫
Yeah, it'll be fine.
So, I can count on you to do well again?
今度も期待していいのよね？
Yeah, it'll be fine.
（圭）
うん　大丈夫
Thanks for breakfast.
ごちそうさま
I'm off.
行ってきます
（ドアの開閉音）
（ため息）
（渡辺(わたなべ)）
永井君 朝から勉強漬け？
Hey, Nagai, cramming so early
in the morning?
まあ 時間がもったいないからね
Well, I need to make the most of my time.
（中島(なかじま)）
さすがは お医者様志望
That's an aspiring doctor for you.
We can't all score in the top ten
of the med school exams.
（渡辺）
医学部模試で１桁順位は違うね〜
God, why do I have to listen to this?
ったく なんで皮肉を
言われなきゃならないんだ
立派な人間になるため
努力してるだけなのに
I'm just working hard to become
an upstanding member of society.
カイ
Kai.
Friend of yours?
（渡辺）
知り合い？
No way. He's a freak.
まさか　変な人だね
（中島）
“変な人”ねえ
A freak, huh?
Maybe he's one of those "Ajins."
（渡辺）
もしかして
あれ“亜人(あじん)”だったりして
（太田(おおた)）
同じ人間とは思えないしね
He sure seems like a different species.
（圭）
僕らには関係ない話だよ
That kind of thing has nothing
to do with us.
（教師）
では 教科書247ページ
Turn to Page 247 in your textbooks,
on the discovery of Ajins.
亜人の発見について
This won't really appear on the exams...
この辺りは受験とは関係なく…
（圭）スルーしてよし
（教師）一般教養として—
-In other words, safe to ignore.
-Just something you should know.
知っておくべき部分だ
みんなも知っているように
亜人は不死身の存在
As you all know,
Ajins are immortal beings.
We're told that they'll never die.
死ぬことがないと言われている
Although we're not sure
if that's absolutely true.
絶対かどうかは
分かっていないがね
We've also heard reports
that they "emit a peculiar voice."
他にも“独特の声を発する”
という報告もあるが—
That's all the information
that's been released to the public.
我々民間に公開されている…
（渡辺）
これ 亜人の実験だって
-I've heard this is an Ajin experiment.
-What?
（中島）
実験？　どうせニセモノだろ
It's probably a fake.
The first confirmation of the Ajins'
existence was 17 years ago in Africa.
亜人が初めて確認されたのは
17年前のアフリカ
ちょうど君たちが生まれた年だな
That's about the same year
you were all born.
He was an immortal soldier called
a "Soldier of God" by the locals.
それは 現地で“神の兵”と
呼ばれた不死身の軍人だった
米軍が拿捕(だほ)したことで
真実と証明されたんだ
After its capture by the U.S. Army,
it was proven to be true.
There were attempts to cover it up,
隠蔽(いんぺい)しようとする動きも
あったようだが—
but it was simply too big
to be able to hide.
事が重大すぎて すぐに露見した
There are currently 46 confirmed Ajins
around the world and two in Japan.
現在 世界で46体
日本では２体の亜人が
確認されているが—
恐らく発見されていない亜人も
いるだろう
But there are probably others
that haven't been discovered yet.
なにせ 死ななければ
分からないわけだから—
After all, there's no way of knowing
unless they die.
今 この場に亜人が存在する
可能性もゼロとは言えん
There's even a possibility
that there's an Ajin in this very room.
Yes, Watanabe.
渡辺君
I heard that you get a massive bounty
if you capture an Ajin.
（渡辺）
亜人を捕獲すると—
ばく大な賞金が手に入るって
聞きましたけど
The bounty may be just a rumor,
but there's probably some kind of reward.
（教師）
賞金はうわさかも知れんが
何らかの報酬はあるだろうね
For example, asserting ownership
over your prey.
例えば 狩猟のように獲物の…
獲物？
Prey?
あっ
（教師）
永井君 何か？
Nagai, did you have something to add?
え いや 何でもありません
No, nothing...
（教師）
何か質問があるんだろ？
You have a question, don't you?
あの… 亜人って
人間じゃないんですか？
So, Ajins aren't human?
は？
Of course not.
当たり前だろう
Of course...
…ですよね
ハハハハ…
（教師）
では次に
亜人の利用価値についてだが…
Anyway, turning to the utility value
of Ajins...
ハハハ…
FRIEND 3: I'M AT THE LIBRARY,
WANNA COME?
I guess it's important to maintain
some level of friendship.
交友関係も ある程度は
大事にしておかないとな
SORRY, I HAVE PREP SCHOOL NOW.
I heard this is an Ajin experiment.
（渡辺）
亜人の実験だって
AJIN EXPERIMENT
Ugh, this is awful.
（圭）
うわっ 最悪
これって…
Could this be...?
（泣き声）
Kei...
（永井慧理子(ながいえりこ)）
お兄ちゃん
Why did he have to die?
なんで この子死んじゃったの？
（泣き声）
お母さんは“不良品だった”って
Mom said he was "defective."
Do you die if you're defective?
不良品だと死んじゃうの？
（圭）
しかたないよ　病気だったんだ
There was nothing we could do.
He was sick.
そういえば
なんで死ぬんだろう？
Come to think of it, why do we die?
It's not like we need to...
別に死ななくても…
誰？
Who are you?!
It's not... like we...
（ＩＢＭ）
別… に… 死…
はっ…
need to...
（ＩＢＭ）
だ… れ…
あっ
（降車ベルの音）
（圭）
調子 いいみたいだな
It looks like you're doing well.
I'm just not doing terrible.
（慧理子）
悪くないだけ
If I was doing well, I wouldn't be here.
調子よかったら
こんなとこ いない
（圭）
あ… そっか
Right...
So, what do you want? Aren't you normally
at prep school right now?
で 何なの？
この時間は
予備校なんじゃないの？
When we were little...
（圭）
小さいころ
犬の墓 作ったことあったろ？
あの時のこと覚えてる？
do you remember burying our dog?
If there's anything you remem--
もし何か覚えてるなら…
フフッ やっぱりね
I knew it.
You wouldn't be here without a reason.
目的がなきゃ来るわけないもんね
Have you seen Kai lately?
最近 カイさんに会った？
（圭）
え？　いや会ってないけど
No, I haven't.
I want to see him again.
カイさんに会いたい
どう？　カイ
-Did you get it, Kai?
-Yeah, I got it!
（海斗(かいと)）
捕ったぞ！
Wow, it's a saw-tooth stag beetle!
（圭）
すごい！
ノコギリクワガタだよ これ！
（笑い声）
Kei, give me your cell phone.
圭ちゃん
お母さんに携帯 渡しなさい
えっ なんで？
Why?
I'm deleting Kaito's information.
（圭の母）
海斗君のアドレス 消すわ
立派な人間になりたいなら
付き合う人間も選びなさい
ADDRESS BOOK: KAITO
You have to choose your friends carefully
if you want to be an upstanding person.
（慧理子）
昔はあんなに仲良かったのに
You used to be so close.
まあ 今はいろいろと忙しいし…
I'm kind of busy lately...
立派になるんだもんね
兄さんは
You're going
to be someone upstanding after all.
So, Eri, you really don't remember?
あのさ 慧理子
ホントに覚えてない？
-When we buried the dog--
-It's too long ago to remember.
犬の墓作った時の…
そんな昔のこと覚えてない
Why don't you just leave already?
Aren't you busy?
もう帰ったら？
忙しいんでしょ？
あ ああ…
Time for your blood draw, Ms. Nagai.
（看護師）
永井さん 採血の時間ですよ
Oh, they're pretty.
あら きれいね
Just throw them out.
（慧理子）
捨ててください
Becoming a fine, upstanding human being.
（圭）
“立派な人間になる”
そのためには
必要なことだけをして—
You have to do only what's necessary.
必要なものだけを選んで…
Choose only what's necessary.
So, I was like--
（渡辺）
それでさぁ… あっ 永井君！
Nagai!
必要じゃないものは…
Anything unnecessary...
Uh, Nagai?
（渡辺）
あれ？　永井君？
has to be cast away.
（圭）
切り捨てなきゃいけないんだ
あれって…
Could that be...?
（衝突音）
あ… ああ…
（運転手）
ああ…
It was a red light.
し… 信号 赤だったよな？
It was that kid's fault, right?
飛び出したガキが
悪いんだよな！？
Was there an accident?
（通行人）
事故か？
え…
（圭）
うっ うう…
あ… ああ… あ…
ち… 違う…
No!
違う！
-An Ajin?
-It's an Ajin.
（通行人）
亜人？
あ… 亜人だよ
（渡辺）
本当にいたなんて…
They really exist.
No...
ち… 違う
No, this isn't...
I'm not!
違う！
これは… 僕は…
This is some kind of mistake!
違うって！
I'm human!
人間… 僕は！
（渡辺）
あ… ああ 信じるよ…
Yeah. I believe you.
I mean, we're friends after all.
友達… だもんね
はっ
-...a massive bounty...
-Ajin aren't human?
（渡辺）
ばく大な賞金が…
人間じゃないんですか？
当たり前だろう
Of course not.
（叫び声）
（中島）
体が…
I can't move...
（渡辺）
動か… ない…
I can't move.
No.
違う…
違う
No.
No!
違う！
（サイレン）
（女性）
それが ただの事故じゃないのよ！
It wasn't any ordinary accident.
It was an Ajin.
（女性）
亜人よ 亜人！
（警官）
ああ 君　ちょっといいかな？
Can I talk to you for a moment?
Do you know someone named Kei Nagai?
永井圭という人物を
知ってるかな？
うん？
Never heard of him.
全然 知らねぇ
何かしたの？　そいつ
What'd he do?
Apparently, he's an Ajin.
その子ねぇ 亜人らしいわよ
-An Ajin?
-It's true!
（女性）あ･じ･ん！
（警官）ちょっと…
（女性）
ホントよ！
生き返るのを見たもの　ねぇ？
I saw him come back to life.
Well, good for him, I guess?
ふーん 興味ねぇわ
Okay, I just wanted to ask
if you knew him.
いや 知らないならいい
圭！
Kei!
はぁっ はぁっ はぁっ…
はぁっ はぁ…
No way. They're already at my house?
そんな…　もう 家の方まで
Where? Where can I run?
どこに… どこに逃げればいい？
FRIEND 1, 2, 3...
誰か　誰か…
Somebody, anybody...
ALL CONTACTS:
FRIEND 12, 13...
Damn it.
駄目だ！　くっ…
あっ…
（海斗）
圭　ほら！
Look, Kei!
あっ…
Kai...
カイ…
KAITO
あっ
（携帯の振動音）
Kei, I've been waiting for you.
圭 待ってたぞ
カイ！
あ あの… どうしよう？
Kai, I...
What do I do?
僕 どうしたら？
落ち着け　今 どこだ？
Calm down. Where are you now?
今？
I... I'm...
今は…
I believe you.
ああ 信じるよ…
あ あの… その…
圭
Kei?
You can trust me.
俺は大丈夫だ
Kai.
カイ…
（幼い圭と海斗の笑い声）
昔 クワガタを捕まえた木の下
Under the tree
where we found that stag beetle.
I'll be right there.
すぐ行く
Kai?
カイ？
はっ ううっ！
あっ
亜人を発見　応援を要請する
Ajin in sight. Requesting backup.
おい 待て！　止まれ！
Hey, wait! Stop!
They're not going to catch me!
No way I'll let them!
追いつかれてたまるか！
はぁっ はぁっ…
（警官）
手荒なまねはしない
I'm not going to hurt you.
Just come out quietly.
おとなしく出てきなさい
はぁっ…
うっ あっ！
がっ… ああっ！
動くな！　動くなよ
Don't move! Don't you move.
ツキ神社付近にて
亜人を確保　亜人確保
I've apprehended
the Ajin near Tsuki Shrine.
-I repeat, I have the Ajin in custody.
-Ajin?
亜人…
くっ…
（海斗）おりゃ！
（警官）がはっ
-Kai--
-Stop!
（圭）カイ！
（海斗）おっと！
名前は言うな
No names.
Can you stand?
立てるか？
あっ…
うん
走るぞ
Time to run.
あ… 亜人が逃走！
The Ajin is on the run!
繰り返す　亜人が逃走！
I repeat, the Ajin is on the run!
He seems to have an accomplice.
仲間が１人いるもよう
検問を要請する！
Requesting roadblocks!
いいか？
-You good?
-Yeah.
ああ
We are live in front of the Ajin's house.
（キャスター）
こちら
亜人の自宅前です
国内３件目の亜人発見
そして 逃亡
This is the third Ajin discovery
and fugitive on Japanese soil.
小さな町は 大きな
騒ぎとなっています
This small town is in an uproar.
I've thought for a long time now
that he didn't seem human.
前から思ってたんですよ
人間っぽくない
やつだって
AJIN DISCOVERED IN CAR ACCIDENT
THIRD CASE IN JAPAN
（荒木(あらき)）
亜人といっても ただのガキだ！
Ajin or not, he's still just a kid!
どうせ遠くまで行けやしない
さっさと確保しろ！
He won't get far.
Hurry up and nab him!
（電話の呼び出し音）
（せきばらい）
Thank you for waiting, I'm Araki
from the Saitama Prefectural Police.
大変お待たせしました
埼玉県警の荒木ですが…
（戸崎優(とさきゆう)）
あなた方は
事態を甘く見すぎている
You're all underestimating the situation.
そう言われましても
捜索には十分な人員を…
But we have plenty
of men conducting the search--
（戸崎）
これは国家レベルの案件です
This is a national issue.
はあ…
（戸崎）
亜人の解明が
進んでいないのは どの国も同じ
Every country has seen efforts
to shed light on the Ajins stalled.
もし あなた方の不手際で—
You are of course aware
what will happen if Kei Nagai
他国に永井圭を
奪われるようなことになれば—
is captured by another country,
due to your negligence?
結果はお分かりでしょう？
あっ…
（ため息）
Double-- No, triple our men!
人員を倍…
いや ３倍に増員しろ！
Do whatever it takes to bring him in!
何が何でも とっ捕まえろ！
（戸崎）
新しい亜人 永井圭
Kei Nagai, our new Ajin.
I won't let you get away.
逃がすわけにはいかんよ
I won't let them catch me.
追いつかれてたまるか
TO BE CONTINUED
願い叶(かな)うなら
もう一度
If my wish would come true
Once again
君の心に
触れていたい
I wanna touch your heart
No matter how dark it gets
どんな闇でも
探してるんだ
I'll be searching
たったひとつの
光を
For my one
And only light
As I look up to the stars
遠いけど
Even though you are far
同じ星空　見上げてる
You're looking up at the same starry sky
心の空には
雫(こぼ)れ落ちそうな
In the sky of my heart
It's about to spill over
君の笑顔と
ぬくもり
Your smile and
Your warmth
Hear me
Until I went away and
Faced the lonely days
愛することの意味なんて
I thought I could understand
What it means to love
分かってたつもりだった
Feeling everything that
Was right in front of me
大切なもの失って
Losing something precious
本当の愛に気付いて
Realizing real love
I'll tell you now,
Just how close you are
I'll tell you now